<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Belle Creek]]></title><description><![CDATA[A website to collect and share information about the Belle Creek Metropolitian District No 1. ]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 20:21:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Oktoberfest 2019]]></title><description><![CDATA[Come and enjoy some beer and brats with neighbors. This beer festival will feature free beer from donors in the community as well as home…]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org/2019/oktoberfest/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bellecreek.org/2019/oktoberfest/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 22:12:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;Come and enjoy some beer and brats with neighbors.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This beer festival will feature free beer from donors in the community as well as home brewed beers.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Use Easements]]></title><description><![CDATA[What is a Use Easement? On either side of your home there is at a minimum, a 5 foot setback from the property line.  Homes developed by New…]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org/2019/use_easements/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bellecreek.org/2019/use_easements/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h1&gt;What is a Use Easement?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On either side of your home there is at a minimum, a 5 foot setback from the property line.  Homes developed by New Town Builders often have what is called a Use Easement on this 5 foot setback.  This means that a property owner gets to use the setback area of the property belonging to their next door neighbor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This use comes with restrictions.  Side yard fencing is not allowed on the side lot line between structures on lots which have a Use Easement.  The owner of the property on which the Use Easement is located has the right, at all reasonable times, to enter the property for the purpose of performing work, accessing electrical panels, air conditioners and other equipment.  The owner benefitting from the Use Easement has to maintain the property and any fence that lies on, or borders the use easement.  Owners benefitting from the Use Easement cannot attach anything to the exterior wall for the home of the adjacent property owner.  Owners benefitting from the Use Easement must not damage the property, structure, or foundation or the adjacent property owner’s property and home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/assets/notices/UseEasements.pdf&quot;&gt;Go here to view a pdf excerpt of Use Easements as described by the Master Declaration of Covenants&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions and/or if you want to find out if there is a Use Easement on your property or if you benefit from a Use Easement, you can call or email Laurie Tatlock.  Direct phone # &lt;a href=&quot;tel:+17202748377&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;720-274-8377&lt;/a&gt;  - email:  &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:laurie@mulhernmre.com&quot;&gt;laurie@mulhernmre.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[December US-85 Public Meeting]]></title><description><![CDATA[There is scheduled a public meeting to discuss the future changes to US-85 to better support the increases in traffic. It will be an open…]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org/2018/2018_december_us85_update/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bellecreek.org/2018/2018_december_us85_update/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;December US-85 Public Meeting&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is scheduled a public meeting to discuss the future changes to US-85 to better support the increases in traffic. It will be an open house event where you can ask questions. It will be held on Wednesday, December 12th from 4:30 pm to 7:00 pm at the Belle Creek Family Center: 10693 Belle Creek Blvd.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can get more details &lt;a href=&quot;//www.codot.gov/library/studies/us-85-from-i-76-to-124th-avenue-highway-design-improvements&quot; target=&quot;cdot-website&quot;&gt;at the CDOT website&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;/notices/2018-US-85-Public-Meeting.pdf&quot; target=&quot;public-meeting&quot;&gt;from the public notice postcard pdf.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Property Annexation]]></title><description><![CDATA[Request for comment and review: property annexation A lot near Belle Creek is requesting to be annexed by Commerce City. The city has asked…]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org/2018/2018_property_annexation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bellecreek.org/2018/2018_property_annexation/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h1&gt;Request for comment and review: property annexation&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lot near Belle Creek is requesting to be annexed by Commerce City. The city has asked for comments from anyone with a concern.
Details are provided in this pdf.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;/notices/commerce-city-lot-annex.pdf&quot;&gt;To learn more, view this pdf notice of commerce city lot annexation.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[October Belle Creek Metro District Meeting Minutes]]></title><description><![CDATA[The October Metro District meeting was held on October 2nd at the family center as regularly scheduled. The topics discussed included the…]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org/2018/2018-10-02-MeetingMinutes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bellecreek.org/2018/2018-10-02-MeetingMinutes/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Minutes of the Meeting of the Board of Directors&lt;br&gt;of&lt;br&gt;Belle Creek Metropolitan District No 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The October Metro District meeting was held on October 2nd at the family center as regularly scheduled. The topics discussed included the YMCA report, the Belle Creek Boulevar Realignment, the 2017 audit and 2018 budget, data protection policies, replacing more backflow valves there were stolen, repairing the family center roof and maintenance needs of the family center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more details checkout the meeting minutes here: &lt;a href=&quot;/notices/2018-10-02-Minutes.pdf&quot; target=&quot;meeting-minutes&quot;&gt;Meeting Minutes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reservoir Mosquitos?!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Reservoir Mosquitos?! Due to the reports of mosquitos near the newly filled Tanabe Reservoir, Denver Water did perform a site visit to…]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org/2018/2018_mosquitos/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bellecreek.org/2018/2018_mosquitos/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h1&gt;Reservoir Mosquitos?!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to the reports of mosquitos near the newly filled Tanabe Reservoir, Denver Water did perform a site visit to further investigate the situation. Staff observed flying insects, identified as non-biting midges, near the water and to a lesser extent near the caretaker’s road. These midges are commonplace throughout the region from spring through fall and are not something that Denver Water would mitigate near a reservoir, as it would require pesticide use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, Denver Water staff took water samples in the reservoir to check for mosquito larvae. The good news is that no mosquito larvae was found. This is consistent with what we would expect, as larvae need extremely still bodies of water to survive. In a reservoir the size of Tanabe, there is sufficient movement in the water to prevent larvae from surviving.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A Call for Nominations]]></title><description><![CDATA[Commerce City “Rules of the Streets” Notice is hereby given that an election will be held on Tuesday, May 8, 2018, between the hours of 7:0…]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org/2018/2018_join_board/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bellecreek.org/2018/2018_join_board/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h1&gt;Commerce City “Rules of the Streets”&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notice is hereby given&lt;/strong&gt; that an election will be held on Tuesday, May 8, 2018, between the hours of 7:00 a.m. and 7:00 p.m. At that time, two (2) directors will be elected to serve four-year terms. Eligible electors of the Belle Creek Metropolitan District No. 1 interested in serving on the board of directors may &lt;a href=&quot;/uploads/2018/Self-NominationForm.rtf&quot;&gt;download a Self-Nomination and Acceptance form &lt;/a&gt; or obtain from the District Designated Election Official (DEO):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;margin-left: 60px;&quot;&gt;
    Laurie Tatlock
    &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/aSdda7WDHd82&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;188 Inverness Drive West, Suite 150
    &lt;br&gt;Englewood, CO  80112&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:laurie@mulhernmre.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;laurie@mulhernmre.com&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;tel:303-649-9857&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;303-649-9857&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Office of the DEO is open on the following days:  Monday – Friday from 8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The deadline to submit a Self-Nomination and Acceptance form is close of business on Friday, March 2, 2018 (no later than 67 days prior to the election).  If the DEO determines that a Self-Nomination and Acceptance form is not sufficient, the eligible elector who submitted the form may amend the form until 5:00 p.m. on the day of the deadline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Affidavit of Intent To Be A Write-In-Candidate forms must be submitted to the office of the DEO by the close of business on Monday, March 5, 2018 (the sixty-fourth day before the election).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notice is further given&lt;/strong&gt; that applications for an absentee ballot shall be filed with the DEO no later than the close of business on Tuesday, May 1, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tanabe Reservoir August Update]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tanabe Reservoir August Update Denver Water has started a $5 million investment into its property next to Belle Creek. This project will…]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org/2017/august_water_district/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bellecreek.org/2017/august_water_district/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h1&gt;Tanabe Reservoir August Update&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Denver Water has started a $5 million investment into its property next to Belle Creek. This project will facilitate future operation of the Tanabe reservoir, which will be located on that land. They are working on the existing fence, putting in private road improvements and adding a few water control structures. Another major part of the project not seen on the following map is a large amount of electrical work that will need to happen before we can operate the reservoir.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../uploads/2017/2017-02-15-TanabeReservoirMap.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;map of updated reservoir&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project started August 29 and will continue until the middle of January 2018. This end date could change depending on when the contractor can get the needed material from their distribution center in Houston. It is still our hope to start filling the reservoir in spring 2018.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Residents can expect an increase in construction traffic and a visible presence of construction at the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first part of the project will be the removal of the 6-foot tall fence running along property lines southeast of the reservoir. They will be removing the current 6-foot tall fence, create a 6-foot rock-covered firebreak and then install a new 8-foot tall fence at the edge of the firebreak (six feet from the current fence position.) The reasons for this change in fencing are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To ensure the safety of the public and to deter individuals from entering the property.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To create a fire break to enhance the safety of the neighborhood from potential grass fires.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To meet perimeter regulations for operational reservoirs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 6-foot strip of land in between the fence and the homes will be maintained by Denver Water. It has been asked that residents do not place anything in that area including personal items (i.e. chairs, plants, storage items), plants or trash. To function as an effective fire break, the area must be kept clear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the contractor has trouble acquiring the 8-foot fence from their distribution center, they will use the 6-foot fence as a temporary place holder until the 8-foot fence arrives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Tanabe Reservoir is part of Denver Water’s downstream reservoir system. For more information, check out &lt;a href=&quot;https://denverwatertap.org/2017/08/30/out-with-the-gravel-in-with-the-water/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Out with the gravel, in with the water&lt;/a&gt; on the website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can call or email Jason Finehout with Denver Water if you have any questions or concerns.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;tel:+13036286352&quot;&gt;303-628-6352&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:jason.finehout@denverwater.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;jason.finehout@denverwater.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Commerce City "Rules of the Streets"]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Covenant Enforcement Committee (CEC) has heard many questions about street parking and traffic problems. School is about to start so we…]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org/2017/2017_street_use_notice/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bellecreek.org/2017/2017_street_use_notice/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;The Covenant Enforcement Committee (CEC) has heard many questions about street parking and traffic problems. School is about to start so we are about to have a lot more cars and kids on the roads. You will likely know most of these, but lets work to keep these streets safe and friendly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../uploads/street_corner.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;a corner in Belle Creek&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are a few things to be aware of:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is against Commerce City laws to park in front of a house that you do not own for longer than 5 hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parking is often contentious in our neighborhood. Most of these rules exist for safety reasons. Here are a few places where it is against Commerce City laws to park:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Within 5 feet of a driveway&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Within 15 feet of a fire hydrant&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Within 20 feet of a crosswalk or intersection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Within 30 feet in front of a stop sign&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The speed limit is 25 miles per hour through the entire community. During school hours the fine for exceeding the speed limit doubles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Commercial vehicles are not allowed on our streets. Our streets are incredibly narrow, so big rigs are likely to get stuck.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to see the details of these laws, you can read them on &lt;a href=&quot;http://c3gov.com&quot; title=&quot;Commerce City Website&quot;&gt;c3gov.com&lt;/a&gt; here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.c3gov.com/home/showdocument?id=816&quot; title=&quot;http://www.c3gov.com/home/showdocument?id=816&quot;&gt;http://www.c3gov.com/home/showdocument?id=816&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Above all, be safe and respectful out there.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Yard Sale 2017 Map]]></title><description><![CDATA[Belle Creek Community Yard Sale Map Come join us for the Belle Creek Community Yard Sale and find yourself some new-to-you clothes…]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org/2017/2017_spring_yard_sale_map/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bellecreek.org/2017/2017_spring_yard_sale_map/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;style&gt;
    .item-table .row.title-row {
        font-weight: bold;
        border-left: none;
        border-right: none;
    }

    .item-table .row {
        border-bottom: 1px #333 solid;
        border-left: 1px #333 solid;
        border-right: 1px #333 solid;
    }
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Belle Creek Community Yard Sale Map&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come join us for the Belle Creek Community Yard Sale and find yourself some new-to-you clothes, kitchenware, toys, tools, knick knacks and much more. Here is a map of all of the locations that registered and a breif summary of things that they will be selling. Children from the community will also be selling snow cones as well as baked goods in the park.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mapcustomizer.com/map/BelleCreekYardSale2017&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Map Customizer View&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../uploads/2017/YardSaleLocations2017.png&quot; alt=&quot;map of yard sales&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;item-table&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row title-row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;Address&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Items for Sale&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;In Community Park&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Girl clothes, boy clothes, baby clothes, baby essentials, toys, grill, rocking chair, houseware items&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;In Community Park&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Kids clothes, adult clothes, and kitchenware&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;In Community Park&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Essential Oil Jewelry, dream catchers&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;In Community Park&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Clothes, kids toys, household items&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;9704 E 105th Ave&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Clothes and knick knacks&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;9676 E 105th Pl&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Girl Toddler Clothes and Toys. Misc house things.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;9518 E 108th Ave&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Books, baby clothing, knick  knacks, adult clothes, Fiberglass Blue Marlin, wall decorations, lots of misc &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;9440 E 106th Ave&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Pop-up trailer, camping utensils, Hot Wheels NIP, misc kitchen and house stuff, adult men and women&apos;s clothes&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;9433 E 108th Ave&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Toys, Shoes, Clothes, Women, Men, Girls, Juniors, Household items&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;9420 E 106th Ave&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Toys/Collectables, Action Figures, Some Kitchen items, pop culture T-shirts (L,XL,XXL)&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;9375 Longs Peak Dr&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Toddler girls clothes and shoes, assorted household items, kids books, toys&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;9273 E 108th Ave&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Clothes toyes furniture&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;9268 E 109th Ave&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Furniture, kitchen items, kid stuff&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;9231 E. 107th Pl&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Furniture, baby items, kids toys, books, movies, antiques, etc&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;9221 E 107th Pl&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Glassware, bedding, (bed spread sets) box spring, bed frame ,misc kitchen items&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;9219 Longs Peak&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Electronics toys small trains stuff&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10927 Beeler Street&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Clothing, shoes, house decor, kitchen items, kids toys&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10908 Dayton Way&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Household items, furniture&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10904 Belle Creek Blvd &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Unlisted&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10902 Beeler St&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Clothes for entire family, baby items, household goods, etc&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10882 Dayton Way&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Baby/Kid Stuff, tools, clothing, electronics &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10872 Dayton Way&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Clothes, DVDs, books, furniture, odds and ends &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10852 Beeler St&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Home and kitchen items; some kids stuff too&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10824 Belle Creek Blvd&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Toys, baby stuff, yard supplies, books&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10822 Dayton Way&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Collectibles, Bling Shirts, Future, Kids Stuff, Kitchen Stuff, Holiday Stuff, Furniture, Movies, Clothes, Children&apos;s Items, Decor, and Collectibles&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10808 Dayton Way&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Unlisted&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10804 Belle Creek Blvd&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;We have Bikes, clothes, Golf Equipment, Furniture, Tools, and Electronics&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10768 Akron Street&lt;br&gt;(in garage in the alley)&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Mens and womens clothing, bags, art work, posters to electronics.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10762 Dayton Way&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Unlisted&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10732 Dayton Way&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Baby yard equipment tools knick knacks&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10664 Belle Creek Blvd&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Furniture, china, cut glass, kitchen items, decorating items, a little of everything&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10618 Dayton Way&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Children&apos;s clothing (sizes 7-12), Belle Creek Charter School shirts (free), shoes, household items, small furniture&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10550 Dayton St&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;Unlisted&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
    </content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Proxy Raffle Winners!]]></title><description><![CDATA[The winner of the $500 home depot gift card is Nicholas Barda.  The winner of the $100 gift card is Ricky Boatman.  The winners of the $5…]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org/2017/2017_proxy_raffle_winners/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bellecreek.org/2017/2017_proxy_raffle_winners/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;The winner of the $500 home depot gift card is Nicholas Barda.  The winner of the $100 gift card is Ricky Boatman.  The winners of the $50 gift card are Donald and Susan Richards.  Congratulations!  Contact Laurie Tatlock at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:laurie@mulhernmre.com&quot;&gt;laurie@mulhernmre.com&lt;/a&gt; to arrange for delivery of your prize. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are still looking for proxies.  We now have 192 of the needed 346.  Please consider sending in a proxy if you have not already done so.  If you have sent in a proxy and would be willing to talk to your neighbors about your decision, please do so.  Proxies can be turned in at the family center, emailed or mailed to Laurie Tatlock, see address below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Laurie Tatlock&lt;br&gt;
Mulhern MRE, Inc.&lt;br&gt;
188 Inverness Drive West, Suite 150&lt;br&gt;
Englewood, CO 80112&lt;br&gt;
phone:  &lt;a href=&quot;tel:+13036499857&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;303-649-9857&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:laurie@mulhernmre.com&quot;&gt;laurie@mulhernmre.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Belle Creek Community Yard Sale 2017]]></title><description><![CDATA[belle creek family center Looking for some gently used baby clothes, kitchen gadgets, tools, toys, or collectables? On Saturday, June 10th…]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org/2017/2017_spring_yard_sale/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bellecreek.org/2017/2017_spring_yard_sale/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../uploads/FamilyCenter1000.png&quot; alt=&quot;belle creek family center&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking for some gently used baby clothes, kitchen gadgets, tools, toys, or collectables? On Saturday, June 10th, Belle Creek will be having a community wide yard sale. If you live in the community it will be a great day to sell things you no longer want or need. Even if you don’t live in the community, come by and see what we are selling. There should be a lot of great finds available all in one small community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to register to sell in yard sale and be part of a map of the participants, then fill out this form: &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/CyHgvb&quot;&gt;https://goo.gl/CyHgvb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing what people discover in our community!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tanabe Reservoir May Update]]></title><description><![CDATA[Denver Water has confirmed that the Tanabe Reservoir project will be constructed starting this July with construction continuing until…]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org/2017/may_water_district/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bellecreek.org/2017/may_water_district/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Denver Water has confirmed that the Tanabe Reservoir project will be constructed starting this July with construction continuing until November.  The exact construction dates should be available in early June.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to expedite the project, they are proposing to work on Saturdays. No Sunday work will occur. The proposed work hours are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7am-5pm Monday through Friday.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8am-4pm on Saturdays.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They have asked for community input.  You can call or email Jason Finehout with Denver Water.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;tel:+13036286352&quot;&gt;303-628-6352&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:jason.finehout@denverwater.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;jason.finehout@denverwater.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spring Cleaning 2017]]></title><description><![CDATA[Time for spring cleaning Get your home and garden ready for the season with the following events. Proof of Commerce City Residency required…]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org/2017/2017_spring/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bellecreek.org/2017/2017_spring/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h1&gt;Time for spring cleaning&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get your home and garden ready for the season with the following events. Proof of Commerce City Residency required at all events. No businesses or contractors allowed. &lt;a href=&quot;http://c3gov.com/trash&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Visit c3gov.com/trash for more information.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Free Landfill Day – Saturday, April 29&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/uploads/2017/2017_landfill_day_spring.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;dl-document&quot;&gt;details (pdf)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
7 a.m. - 3 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Republic Services Tower Landfill&lt;br&gt;
8480 Tower Road&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One load FREE per resident&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No electronics, tires, or hazardous materials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Household Chemical Roundup – Saturday, May 6&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/uploads/2017/2017_chemical_round_spring.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;dl-document&quot;&gt;details (pdf)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Hosted by Tri-County Health Department&lt;br&gt;
9 a.m. - 3 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Hyland Hills Water World&lt;br&gt;
8801 N. Pecos Street, Federal Heights&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;$25 per vehicle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accepted items include: oil, antifreeze, tires, car batteries, home and garden chemicals, fluorescent light bulbs, paint, etc. (details at TCHD.org)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Green Yard Waste Drop-Off Event – Saturday, May 13&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/uploads/2017/2017_green_yard_waste_event_spring.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;dl-document&quot;&gt;details (pdf)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
8 a.m. - 1 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Former Mile High Greyhound Park site - Enter at E. 62nd Avenue and Parkway Drive&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;FREE for all residents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bring compostable plant waste such as grass clippings, tree limbs, leaves, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spring Meeting 2017]]></title><description><![CDATA[Belle Creek Community ANNUAL MEETING AGENDA Saturday – May 6, 2017 – 10:00 a.m.
Belle Creek Family Center
10693 Belle Creek Boulevard…]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org/2017/2017_spring_meeting/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bellecreek.org/2017/2017_spring_meeting/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h1&gt;Belle Creek Community&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;ANNUAL MEETING AGENDA&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Saturday – May 6, 2017 – 10:00 a.m.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/x2iVpMwPrCK2&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Belle Creek Family Center&lt;br&gt;
10693 Belle Creek Boulevard&lt;br&gt;
Henderson, CO 80640&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;tel:+13032893584&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;303.289.3584&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The meeting agenda will include the following matters:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;1. Commerce City Police&lt;br&gt;Officer Ricky Evans&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10:00-10:20&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;2. Commerce City Trash and Recycling&lt;br&gt;Stacie Rieber&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10:20-10:40&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;3. Covenant Enforcement Committee&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10:40-10:50&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;4. YMCA&lt;br&gt;Giovanni Forrest&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;10:50-11:05&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;5. HOA Dissolution&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;11:05-11:15&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;6. Community Outreach Website&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;11:15-11:30&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;7. Community Comments/Concerns/Questions&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-8&quot;&gt;8. Adjournment&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-4&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;District Manager&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Laurie Tatlock&lt;br&gt;
2 Inverness Drive East, Suite 200&lt;br&gt;
Englewood, CO 80112&lt;br&gt;
Email: &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:laurie@mulhernmre.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;laurie@mulhernmre.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Phone # &lt;a href=&quot;tel:+13036499857&quot;&gt;303-649-9857&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Covenant Manager&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Charles Wolfersberger&lt;br&gt;
P.O. Box 8&lt;br&gt;
Henderson, CO 80640&lt;br&gt;
Email: &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:charles@wolfersbergerllc.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;charles@wolfersbergerllc.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Phone # &lt;a href=&quot;tel:+17205417725&quot;&gt;720-541-7725&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New Belle Creek Website: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bellecreekmd.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;www.bellecreekmd.org&lt;a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Newtown Home Window Warranty and Supplier Information]]></title><description><![CDATA[EDIT - It has been reported that “Atrium Windows and Doors” now answers the phone as “Prime Window Sales” and no longer do after warranty…]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org/2017/newtown_windows/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bellecreek.org/2017/newtown_windows/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;[EDIT] - It has been reported that “Atrium Windows and Doors” now answers the phone as “Prime Window Sales” and no longer do after warranty work with residents - only builders. They suggested that you call Glass Unlimited: &lt;a href=&quot;tel:+17204274085&quot;&gt;720-427-4085&lt;/a&gt;. The metro district has not worked with Glass Unlimited, it is the recommendation of Prime Window Sales.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There have been questions about the Warranty for windows in Newtown Homes (the original builder in the community). Here is a little info about the window warranty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Atrium Windows and Doors&lt;br /&gt;
12775 East 38th Avenue&lt;br /&gt;
Denver, Colorado 80239&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;tel:+18003755570&quot;&gt;1-800-375-5570&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.atrium.com&quot;&gt;www.atrium.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Warranty Coverage:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supplier generally warrants the windows for 25 years&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;year 1 is fully covered for parts and installation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;years 2-5 parts only, installation charges apply&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;years 6-15 a 50% charge for parts, installation charges apply&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;years 16-25 a 75% charge for parts, installation charges apply&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tanabe Reservoir Update]]></title><description><![CDATA[The final construction at this site, which will occur from July to November of 2017, is a $5 million investment into the property that will…]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org/2017/water_district/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bellecreek.org/2017/water_district/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;The final construction at this site, which will occur from July to November of 2017, is a $5 million investment into the property that will facilitate future operation of the reservoir. As you can see from the map, Denver Water is working on the existing fence, putting in road improvements and adding a few water control structures. Another major part of the project not seen on the map is a large amount of electrical work that will need to happen before they can operate the reservoir.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../uploads/2017/2017-02-15-TanabeReservoirMap.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;map of updated reservoir&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They will be replacing the fence running along property lines adjacent to Belle Creek homes, southeast of the reservoir. They will remove the current 6’ fence, create a 6’ rock-covered fire break and then install a new 8’ fence at the edge of the firebreak (6’ from the current fence position.) The reasons for this change in fencing are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To ensure the safety of the public and to deter individuals from entering the property.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To create a fire break to enhance the safety of the neighborhood from potential grass fires.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To meet perimeter regulations for operational reservoirs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Residents can expect an increase in construction traffic and a visible presence of construction at the site. Feel free to contact Laurie Tatlock if you have questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;tel:+3036499857&quot;&gt;303-649-9857&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:laurie@mulhernmre.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;laurie@mulhernmre.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dissolution]]></title><description><![CDATA[Masters Association Dissolution Belle Creek Metropolitan District No. 1 (“District”) staff and legal counsel have advised the District Board…]]></description><link>https://bellecreek.org/2016/dissolution/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://bellecreek.org/2016/dissolution/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h1&gt;Masters Association Dissolution&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Belle Creek Metropolitan District No. 1 (“District”) staff and legal counsel have advised the District Board that it would be a good idea to dissolve the Belle Creek Master Association (“Association”). This Association is no longer active, but it costs thousands of dollars per year to operate. If dissolved, this community will keep all of the same rules that it has today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below are links to the important documents including the Proposed Declaration and the Termination Agreement. You can also get copies from family center staff. The proxy form allows the board to vote on your behalf to end the Master Association and update some documents related to this change. Since 2008, the District has been doing everything that the Association was created to do but it requires a community vote to end the Association. This is what we are trying to do now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please read the following documents to learn more about the proposed dissolution of the  Association including why it is being suggested. If you have more questions, come to the next Covenant Enforcement Committee meeting. These meetings are held every third Wednesday of the month at 6pm in the Family Center. You may also call or email Laurie Tatlock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/assets/dissolution/ProxyForMeetingToVoteOnHOADissolution.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;dl-document&quot;&gt;Proxy for the meeting to vote on Masters Association dissolution&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/assets/dissolution/DraftDeclaration.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;dl-document&quot;&gt;Amended and Restated Master Declaration of Covenants, Conditions and Restrictions of Belle Creek&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/assets/dissolution/Termination_Agreement_of_Belle_Creek.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;dl-document&quot;&gt;Termination Agreement of Belle Creek, A Common Interest Community&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/assets/dissolution/DissolutionExplanationLetter.docx&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;dl-document&quot;&gt;An explanation of the dissolution including a brief history&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/assets/dissolution/DissolutionExecutiveSummary.docx&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;dl-document&quot;&gt;The email sent out notifying Belle Creek residents of these changes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>